(Howard:)What would Summer Glau
be doing riding the train?
(Leonard:)Maybe John Connor's aboard and she's
protecting him from an evil Terminator.
(Sheldon:)Unlikely.
That's a television show, Leonard.
(Leonard:)Thank you.
If Skynet did exist in the future, a perfect
way to infiltrate and destroy mankind...
(Sheldon:)...would be to send Terminators back
as actors...
(Sheldon:)...who have played Terminators
in films and television...
(Sheldon:)...lulling us into a false sense
of security, i.e.:
"That's Summer Glau
from The Sarah Connor Chronicles.
(Sheldon:)No, Summer, don't kill me!
I'm pro-robot."
[GROANING]
(Leonard:)At least he's off the train crap.
[TRAIN STARTING]
SHELDON:
Wheeee.
(Howard:)Sheldon, I owe you an apology.
(Howard:)Taking the train was a stroke of brilliance.
I've actually got a shot at a Terminator.
Please. When it comes to Terminators...
(Raj:)...you've got a better shot of scoring
with Arnold Schwarzenegger.
(Howard:)You're overlooking something.
(Howard:)I have 11 hours with her
in a confined space.